import 'package:flutter/material.dart';
import 'modal.dart';

List<Questionbank> questionbank = <Questionbank>[
  Questionbank(
      id: 1, question: " Indian national animal is tiger ", ans: true),
  Questionbank(
      id: 2, question: " c language is world's first language ", ans: false),
  Questionbank(id: 3,
      question: " Google's parent company is called Alphabet ",
      ans: true),
  Questionbank(
      id: 4, question: " Indian national flower is Rose ", ans: false),
  Questionbank(id: 5,
      question: " Indian national fruit is mango ",
      ans: true),
  Questionbank(
      id: 6, question: " c language is created by John knoll ", ans: false),
  Questionbank(
      id: 7, question: " Cricket is national sport of India ", ans: false),
  Questionbank(id: 8, question: " India have 29 states ", ans: true),
  Questionbank(id: 9, question: " India has 7 Union territories", ans: true),
  Questionbank(id: 10,
      question: " India's total area is 3.0 millian sq.km",
      ans: false),
  Questionbank(id: 11,
      question: " - ",
      ans: false),
];

